http://www.dundeelaw.com/privacy-policy

303 W. Main Street, West Dundee, IL 60118 | 847-428-7725Call for a Free ConsultationEvening and Weekend Hours by Appointment
100 Illinois Street, Suite 200, St. Charles, IL 60174 | 630-200-4882By Appointment OnlyEvening and Weekend Hours by Appointment
Uncontested Divorce
Allocation of Parental Responsibilities (Custody)
Parenting Time (Formerly Visitation)
Privacy Policy
This statement applies to the online collection of personal information via websites operated by and applications offered by the Law Offices of Benedict Schwarz, II P.C. Details of the Privacy Statement follow immediately below.
What personal information is collected and how is that information used?
We collect information about our users in three ways: directly from the user (such as when ordering a product, registering an account or signing up for a newsletter), from our Web server logs, and through cookies.
We use the information primarily to provide you with a personalized Internet experience that delivers the information, resources, and services that are most relevant and helpful to you.
We do not share any of the information you provide with others, unless we say so in this Privacy Statement, or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.
How is my personal information protected?
We have implemented certain appropriate security measures to help protect your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure.
However, please note that we cannot guarantee that unauthorized persons will always be unable to defeat our security measures.
Also, please note that we may store and process your personal information in systems located outside of your home country. Regardless of where these activities occur, we take appropriate steps to ensure that your information is protected consistent with the principles set forth under this Privacy Statement.
Who has access to the personal information?
We will not sell, rent, or lease mailing lists or other customer data to others, and we will not make your personal information available to any unaffiliated parties, except our approved agents and contractors, or as otherwise described in this Privacy Statement.
We rely on some of our affiliates for support of the products and services we offer, and we share some of our back-office functions with other companies. Our affiliates are all required to preserve the confidentiality of any personal information they may access.
We will not disclose any personal information or information about your usage of our websites to unaffiliated third parties, except as necessary to service the account, to enforce the terms of use, to meet our obligations to content and technology providers, or as required by law.
How may I correct, amend or delete my personal information, or update my preferences?
You may cancel your registration or update your preferences at any time simply by contacting us.
If you do not want to receive information about our products or services, please contact us.
If you have any additional questions or concerns related to this statement and/or our practices, please contact us at:
Law Offices of Benedict Schwarz, II P.C.
303 W. Main StreetWest Dundee, IL 60118Phone: 847-428-7725
Practice Areas
DivorceContested DivorceUncontested DivorceAllocation of Parental Responsibilities (Custody)Parenting Time (Formerly Visitation)Alimony/Maintenance/Spousal SupportChild SupportAsset DivisionForensic Accounting and Hidden AssetsRetirement Assets in DivorceTax Implications of DivorceHigh Net Worth DivorceComplex Divorce IssuesLegal SeparationPost Judgment Order ModificationPost Judgment Order EnforcementFAQsFamily LawPaternity & ParentagePrenuptial & Postnuptial AgreementsRelated AdoptionDomestic Violence & Orders of ProtectionMediationReal EstateEstate PlanningWillsLiving TrustsPower of Attorney
Recent Blog Posts
Will I Be Expected to Pay Child Support After My Illinois Divorce?
How Will My Illinois Divorce Affect My Children?
How Can I Adopt My Stepchild in Illinois?
How Can an Illinois Divorce Affect My Retirement?
Why Is a Prenuptial Agreement Important in a Second Marriage?
303 W. Main Street, West Dundee, IL 60118Phone: 847-428-7725Evening and Weekend Hours by AppointmentView Map
100 Illinois Street, Suite 200, St. Charles, IL 60174Phone: 630-200-4882By Appointment OnlyView Map
For a free consultation with one of our skilled divorce and family law attorneys, contact our office today at 847-428-7725. We serve clients in Kane County, McHenry County, DuPage County, Cook County/Rolling Meadows, Algonquin, Barrington, Barrington Hills, Batavia, Bull Valley, Burlington, Campton Hills, Carpentersville, Cary, Crystal Lake, Dundee, East Dundee, Elgin, Geneva, Lake in the Hills, Pingree Grove, St. Charles, South Elgin, West Chicago, West Dundee, Woodstock, and the surrounding Illinois communities.
© 2020 Law Offices of Benedict Schwarz, II P.C.303 W. Main Street, West Dundee, IL 60118847-428-7725
Resources |
Privacy Policy
Disclaimer |
Sitemap
